A sky big enough to fill the heart.
Big Sky River is a tv movie, comedy, romance film directed by Peter Benson.
Tara needs to go back to Parable, Montana, the place that made her the
happiest, in order to move forward after a messy divorce.
Her handsome neighbor presents an unexpected twist.
Tara, played by Emmanuelle Vaugier.
Boone, played by Kavan Smith.
Hutch, played by Lochlyn Munro.
Erin, played by Cassidy Nugent.
Casey, played by Michelle Harrison.
Griffin, played by John JJ Miller.
The Big Sky is a 1952 American Western film produced and directed by Howard Hawks and
written by Dudley Nichols, based on the novel of the same name by A.B.
Guthrie Jr.
The film does not have the same tragic ending as the book.
The cast includes Kirk Douglas, Dewey Martin, Elizabeth Threatt and Arthur
Hunnicutt, who was nominated for an Academy Award for Best Supporting Actor.
Though not considered among Hawks's major achievements by most critics, the film was chosen
by Jonathan Rosenbaum for his alternative list of the Top 100 American Films.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and mind_bending.